<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ThirtyDaysApp</string>

    <string name='title1'>Atomic Habits</string>
    <string name='title2'>The High-Conflict Couple</string>
    <string name='title3'>Mating in Captivity</string>
    <string name='title4'>Eat to Beat Depression and Anxiety</string>
    <string name='title5'>How to Change</string>
    <string name='title6'>Maybe You Should Talk To Someone</string>
    <string name='title7'>Connect</string>
    <string name='title8'>Resurrecting Sex</string>
    <string name='title9'>The Law of Success</string>
    <string name='title10'>Remember</string>
    <string name='title11'>Open</string>
    <string name='title12'>Weird</string>
    <string name='title13'>Your Brain Is Always Listening</string>
    <string name='title14'>Nine Lives</string>
    <string name='title15'>Minor Feelings</string>
    <string name='title16'>The First-Time Manager</string>
    <string name='title17'>Late Bloomers</string>
    <string name='title18'>Hood Feminism</string>
    <string name='title19'>Not Born Yesterday</string>
    <string name='title20'>Black-and-White Thinking</string>
    <string name='title21'>How to Thrive in the Virtual Workplace</string>
    <string name='title22'>Born to Win</string>
    <string name='title23'>The Squiggly Career</string>
    <string name='title24'>The Soul of a Woman</string>
    <string name='title25'>Clearer, Closer, Better</string>
    <string name='title26'>In the Name of Identity</string>
    <string name='title27'>Opening Up</string>
    <string name='title28'>Listen Like You Mean It</string>
    <string name='title29'>The Mastery of Love</string>
    <string name='title30'>Deeper Dating</string>

    <string name='desc1'>Atomic Habits by James Clear is a self-help book that provides a framework for building good habits and breaking bad ones. It offers practical strategies for making small, consistent changes that can lead to significant personal growth.</string>
    <string name='desc2'>"The High-Conflict Couple" by Alan E. Fruzzetti is a comprehensive guide for couples struggling with intense, emotionally-charged conflicts. The book offers practical tools and strategies for communication, problem-solving, and emotional regulation to improve relationship satisfaction.</string>
    <string name='desc3'>Mating In Captivity by Esther Perel is a thought-provoking exploration of the challenges and complexities of maintaining desire in long-term relationships.</string>
    <string name='desc4'>Eat to Beat Depression and Anxiety by Drew Ramsey offers a holistic approach to mental health through nutrition. Drawing on scientific research, it provides practical advice on how to use food to support brain function and improve mood.</string>
    <string name='desc5'>How to Change by Katy Milkman is a practical guide to achieving personal goals. It explores the science of motivation and offers actionable tips on how to overcome obstacles, create good habits, and stay on track towards success.</string>
    <string name='desc6'>Maybe You Should Talk To Someone by Lori Gottlieb is a memoir highlighting the transformative power of therapy through the author\'s personal journey and experiences working as a therapist. The book guides readers to better understand themselves and others while offering insight into the therapeutic process.</string>
    <string name='desc7'>Connect by David Bradford and Carole Robin is a guide to building strong relationships by fostering genuine human connections. The book gives actionable insights and tools to navigate conflict, build trust, and create meaningful relationships both in one\'s personal and professional life.</string>
    <string name='desc8'>Resurrecting Sex by David Schnarch is a guide to help couples overcome sexual difficulties and experience more satisfying intimacy by exploring their individual eroticism and developing emotional intimacy.</string>
    <string name='desc9'>The Law of Success by Napoleon Hill is a timeless self-help book that offers practical strategies for achieving success in life. It provides a comprehensive framework for overcoming obstacles, developing self-discipline, and mastering the art of persuasion and leadership.</string>
    <string name='desc10'>Remember by Lisa Genova is a heart-wrenching story about a young woman suffering from early-onset Alzheimer\'s disease. Through her experiences, the book provides insight into the disease and its impact on families and loved ones.</string>
    <string name='desc11'>Open by Johan Norberg explores how openness has contributed to human progress, innovation, and prosperity throughout history. It argues that globalization, immigration, and free trade have brought unprecedented opportunities for individuals and societies to thrive.</string>
    <string name='desc12'>"Weird" by Olga Khazan explores how unusual behavior and perspectives can lead to personal and societal benefits. The book challenges conventional thinking and encourages readers to embrace their quirks.</string>
    <string name='desc13'>"Your Brain Is Always Listening" by Daniel G. Amen explores how to tame the dragons in our minds that may be causing anxiety, depression or other mental health issues. The book provides practical tips to regain control of our thoughts, emotions and actions.</string>
    <string name='desc14'>Nine Lives by William Dalrymple is a collection of nine biographical stories of individuals from different backgrounds in India. The book explores their unique lives and spiritual journeys, offering a glimpse into the diverse religious landscape of the country.</string>
    <string name='desc15'>Minor Feelings by Cathy Park Hong is a powerful essay collection that explores Asian American identity and the complex emotions that arise from it. Through personal stories and cultural analysis, Hong exposes the racial barriers and ingrained prejudices that continue to affect Asian Americans today.</string>
    <string name='desc16'>UThe First-Time Manager by Loren B. Belker, Jim McCormick, and Gary S. Topchik provides a practical guide for new managers. It covers essential skills such as communication, delegation, motivation, and team-building.</string>
    <string name='desc17'>Late Bloomers by Rich Karlgaard is a non-fiction book that challenges our cultural assumptions about the ideal path to success. It celebrates the power of individuality and the potential of late blooming, proving that success comes in many different forms and at different stages of life.</string>
    <string name='desc18'>Hood Feminism by Mikki Kendall challenges mainstream feminism and advocates for a more inclusive movement that addresses issues faced by marginalized women. The book highlights the importance of recognizing intersectionality and fighting for social justice for all women.</string>
    <string name='desc19'>"Not Born Yesterday" by Hugo Mercier explores why humans are better at detecting deception than creating it. The book argues that our skepticism and ability to reason evolved as a social tool, helping us navigate tricky social situations.</string>
    <string name='desc20'>"Black-and-White Thinking" by Kevin Dutton explores the dangers of rigid, all-or-nothing thinking and offers practical ways to develop more nuanced, flexible perspectives. It helps readers better navigate complex situations and relationships.</string>
    <string name='desc21'>"How to Thrive in the Virtual Workplace" by Robert Glazer with Mick Sloan is a practical guide for navigating remote work. It provides actionable steps for adapting to a virtual environment and achieving success while working remotely.</string>
    <string name='desc22'>Born to Win by Zig Ziglar and Tom Ziglar is a motivational book that provides a step-by-step guide on how to succeed in life and business. It offers practical tips, strategies, and stories to help readers unlock their potential and achieve their goals.</string>
    <string name='desc23'>The Squiggly Career by Helen Tupper and Sarah Ellis is a guide to navigating the modern career landscape with its twists, turns, and possibilities. It provides actionable advice for identifying and pursuing fulfilling and purpose-driven careers in the age of increasing uncertainty and rapid change.</string>
    <string name='desc24'>The Soul of a Woman by Isabel Allende is a personal reflection exploring the connections between feminism, family, and personal history. Allende shares her experiences and honors the women who have influenced her life.</string>
    <string name='desc25'>Clearer, Closer, Better by Emily Balcetis is a psychology book about perception, its limitations and how to overcome them. It helps us see challenges in a new light and improve our mental imagery and motivation to reach our goals.</string>
    <string name='desc26'>In the Name of Identity by Amin Maalouf is a thought-provoking exploration of the roots of identity, how they are formed, and how they can be used and abused. It offers insight into the complexities of individual and group identity in a globalized world.</string>
    <string name='desc27'>Opening Up by Tristan Taormino is a guidebook for individuals and couples interested in exploring consensual non-monogamy. It provides practical advice on communication, negotiation, and building strong relationships in ethical non-monogamous communities.</string>
    <string name='desc28'>"Listen Like You Mean It" by Ximena Vengoechea is a practical guide for improving communication skills. It explains how to hear what others are saying, ask better questions and create stronger relationships through active listening.</string>
    <string name='desc29'>CThe Mastery of Love by Don Miguel Ruiz with Janet Mills is a guide to cultivate self-love and build healthy relationships by learning the truth about ourselves and love. It offers practical wisdom to facilitate self-discovery and lead to lasting happiness.</string>
    <string name='desc30'>Deeper Dating by Ken Page is a guide to finding meaningful connections in love. He shows readers how to embrace their core gifts and vulnerabilities to find deeper and more fulfilling relationships, rather than settling for surface-level interactions.</string>

    <string name="expand_button">Expand Button to view description of each day</string>
    <string name="days_30">30 Days of Reading</string>
</resources>